SENTENCES,ANNOTED DATA
Familiar with various development languages like Django (Python) and PHP and deployment platforms like GCP and AWS,"(""Familiar with various development languages like Django (Python) and PHP and deployment platforms like GCP and AWS."",{""entities"":[(281,287,""TECH_SKILLS""),(314,320,""TECH_SKILLS""),(351,354,""TECH_SKILLS""),(410,413,""TECH_SKILLS""),(443,446,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"MIT Academy of Engineering, Pune"",{""entities"":[(149,160,""COLLEGE""),(185,196,""EDUCATION","(""MIT Academy of Engineering, Pune"",{""entities"":[(149,160,""COLLEGE""),(185,196,""EDUCATION""),(221,225,""LOCATION"")]})"
Software Developer Intern,"(""Software Developer Intern"",{""entities"":[(142,167,""JOB_ROLE"")]})"
"Just Get IT, Mumbai","(""Just Get IT, Mumbai"",{""entities"":[(136,147,""ORGANIZATION""),(175,181,""LOCATION"")]})"
"Recognized the need for an intuitive Product Upload form and hence developed it using JavaScript, AJAX and backend in Django/Python. Solved all the errors and rectified it according to clients needs","(""Recognized the need for an intuitive Product Upload form and hence developed it using JavaScript, AJAX and backend in Django/Python. Solved all the errors and rectified it according to clients needs."",{""entities"":[(203,213,""TECH_SKILLS""),(240,244,""TECH_SKILLS""),(285,291,""TECH_SKILLS""),(317,323,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Developed a Resume Parser using Machine Learning and Hard-Coding it to achieve nearly 75% accuracy.,"(""Developed a Resume Parser using Machine Learning and Hard-Coding it to achieve nearly 75% accuracy."",{""entities"":[(158,174,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Full Stack Developer Intern 2019-05 2019-08 Analytics Domain, Pune","(""Full Stack Developer Intern 2019-05 2019-08 Analytics Domain, Pune"",{""entities"":[(144,171,""JOB_ROLE""),(210,226,""ORGANIZATION""),(254,258,""LOCATION"")]})"
Worked on Online Essay Grading Website using Machine Learning with Django framework. Focused on creating a prediction model using NLP and Neutral Networks.,"(""Worked on Online Essay Grading Website using Machine Learning with Django framework. Focused on creating a prediction model using NLP and Neutral Networks."",{""entities"":[(257,273,""TECH_SKILLS""),(304,320,""TECH_SKILLS""),(392,395,""TECH_SKILLS""),(425,441,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Connected the Python backend to PHP framework using REST APIs. Deployed the Python backend to GCP Compute Engine and created database on Cloud SQL,"(""Connected the Python backend to PHP framework using REST APIs. Deployed the Python backend to GCP Compute Engine and created database on Cloud SQL."",{""entities"":[(224,230,""TECH_SKILLS""),(312,321,""TECH_SKILLS""),(361,367,""TECH_SKILLS""),(404,422,""TECH_SKILLS""),(478,481,""TECH_SKILLS""),(367,370,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Software Development, CPP, Python, Java, R, JS, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, Pig Latin, Data Science, Hadoop, Machine Learning, Talend, Tableau, Version Control Tools, Linux, NodeJS, ReactJS, Django, Java Web, WebRTC, Socket Programming, AWS, Google Cloud, Agile Development, SDLC, DBMS, OS, Networks.","(""Software Development, CPP, Python, Java, R, JS, HTML, CSS, PHP, SQL, Pig Latin, Data Science, Hadoop, Machine Learning, Talend, Tableau, Version Control Tools, Linux, NodeJS, ReactJS, Django, Java Web, WebRTC, Socket Programming, AWS, Google Cloud, Agile Development, SDLC, DBMS, OS, Networks."",{""entities"":[(139,142,""TECH_SKILLS""),(169,175,""TECH_SKILLS""),(202,206,""TECH_SKILLS""),(233,234,""TECH_SKILLS""),(261,263,""TECH_SKILLS""),(296,299,""TECH_SKILLS""),(315,319,""TECH_SKILLS""),(351,354,""TECH_SKILLS""),(381,384,""TECH_SKILLS""),(411,420,""TECH_SKILLS""),(447,459,""TECH_SKILLS""),(486,492,""TECH_SKILLS""),(519,535,""TECH_SKILLS""),(562,568,""TECH_SKILLS""),(595,602,""TECH_SKILLS""),(678,683,""OPERATING_SYSTEM""),(715,721,""TECH_SKILLS""),(748,755,""TECH_SKILLS""),(782,788,""TECH_SKILLS""),(815,823,""TECH_SKILLS""),(850,856,""TECH_SKILLS""),(883,901,""TECH_SKILLS""),(928,931,""TECH_SKILLS""),(958,970,""TECH_SKILLS""),(997,1014,""DEV_METHODOLOGY""),(1046,1050,""DEV_METHODOLOGY"")]})"
Video Conferencing Application with Gaming using WebRTC,"(""Video Conferencing Application with Gaming using WebRTC"",{""entities"":[(221,227,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Data De-duplication in BTRFS in Linux Kernel,"(""Data De-duplication in BTRFS in Linux Kernel"",{""entities"":[(193,205,""OPERATING_SYSTEM"")]})"
"Clustering, Classification and Regression Case study in R programming","(""Clustering, Classification and Regression Case study in R programming"",{""entities"":[(242,243,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Case Study of HealthCare using Hadoop (Pig, Hive)","(""Case Study of HealthCare using Hadoop (Pig, Hive)"",{""entities"":[(180,190,""DOMAIN""),(217,223,""TECH_SKILLS""),(250,253,""TECH_SKILLS""),(280,284,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Ram Kumar G/14, Sunset Heights 53 Juhu Tara Road","(""Ram Kumar G/14, Sunset Heights 53 Juhu Tara Road"",{""entities"":[(126,135,""PERSON_NAME""),(199,205,""PERSON_NAME""),(238,249,""PERSON_NAME"")]})"
Adhiksha Thorat Student of Computer Engineering,"(""Adhiksha Thorat Student of Computer Engineering"",{""entities"":[(132,147,""PERSON_NAME""),(184,204,""EDUCATION"")]})"
LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/adhiksha-thorat,"(""LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/adhiksha-thorat"",{""entities"":[(158,166,""ORGANIZATION"")]})"
Marketing and Sales Professional,"(""Marketing and Sales Professional"",{""entities"":[(149,168,""DOMAIN"")]})"
Masters Business Administration,"(""Masters Business Administration"",{""entities"":[(149,180,""EDUCATION"")]})"
Symbiosis Institute of Management Studies,"(""Symbiosis Institute of Management Studies"",{""entities"":[(158,199,""COLLEGE""),(237,241,""LOCATION""),(265,276,""LOCATION"")]})"
Deccan College of Engineering & Technology,"(""Deccan College of Engineering & Technology"",{""entities"":[(159,201,""COLLEGE""),(246,255,""LOCATION""),(279,288,""LOCATION"")]})"
"DPS Bokaro CBSE Board New Delhi, Delhi","(""DPS Bokaro CBSE Board New Delhi, Delhi"",{""entities"":[(172,181,""LOCATION""),(205,210,""LOCATION"")]})"
Sales Manager,"(""Sales Manager"",{""entities"":[(130,143,""JOB_ROLE"")]})"
"Solvent Solutions Pvt Ltd Kolkata, West Bangal","(""Solvent Solutions Pvt Ltd Kolkata, West Bangal"",{""entities"":[(142,167,""ORGANIZATION""),(194,201,""LOCATION""),(225,236,""LOCATION"")]})"
"Team Leader Serena Global Pvt Ltd  Gurgaon, Delhi-NCR","(""Team Leader Serena Global Pvt Ltd Gurgaon,Delhi-NCR"",{""entities"":[(166,177,""JOB_ROLE""),(200,221,""ORGANIZATION""),(248,255,""LOCATION""),(278,287,""LOCATION"")]})"
"Sales Assistant Tamcoj Technologies Pimpri-Pune, Maharashtra","(""Sales Assistant Tamcoj Technologies Pimpri-Pune, Maharashtra"",{""entities"":[(132,147,""JOB_ROLE""),(170,189,""ORGANIZATION""),(216,227,""LOCATION""),(251,262,""LOCATION"")]})"
Word 2010 Excel 2010 Power Point 2010,"(""Word 2010 Excel 2010 Power Point 2010"",{""entities"":[(126,135,""TECH_SKILLS""),(161,171,""TECH_SKILLS""),(197,213,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Alice Clark AI / Machine Learning Developer,"(""Alice Clark AI / Machine Learning Developer"",{""entities"":[(128,139,""PERSON_NAME""),(165,196,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Experience in database designing, scalability, back-up and recovery, writing and optimizing SQL code and Stored Procedures, creating functions, views, triggers and indexes. Cloud platform: Worked on Microsoft Azure cloud services like Document DB, SQL Azure, Stream Analytics, Event hub, Power BI, Web Job, Web App, Power BI, Azure data lake analytics(U-SQL)","(""Experience in database designing, scalability, back-up and recovery, writing and optimizing SQL code and Stored Procedures, creating functions, views, triggers and indexes. Cloud platform: Worked on Microsoft Azure cloud services like Document DB, SQL Azure, Stream Analytics, Event hub, Power BI, Web Job, Web App, Power BI, Azure data lake analytics(U-SQL)"",{""entities"":[(299,302,""TECH_SKILLS""),(337,354,""TECH_SKILLS""),(456,471,""TECH_SKILLS""),(517,528,""TECH_SKILLS""),(555,564,""TECH_SKILLS""),(609,618,""TECH_SKILLS""),(644,653,""TECH_SKILLS""),(698,706,""TECH_SKILLS""),(732,764,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Software Engineer Microsoft Bangalore, Karnataka","(""Software Engineer Microsoft Bangalore, Karnataka"",{""entities"":[(134,151,""JOB_ROLE""),(174,183,""ORGANIZATION""),(210,219,""LOCATION""),(243,252,""LOCATION"")]})"
Indian Institute of Technology Mumbai,"(""Indian Institute of Technology Mumbai"",{""entities"":[(155,186,""COLLEGE""),(207,213,""LOCATION"")]})"
"Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, and Big Data Handling","(""Machine Learning, Natural Language Processing, and Big Data Handling"",{""entities"":[(185,201,""TECH_SKILLS""),(228,255,""TECH_SKILLS""),(286,294,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Microsoft rewards is loyalty program that rewards Users for browsing and shopping online.,"(""Microsoft rewards is loyalty program that rewards Users for browsing and shopping online."",{""entities"":[(198,207,""ORGANIZATION"")]})"
Kevin Harry SENIOR ANALYST,"(""Kevin HarrySENIOR ANALYST"",{""entities"":[(143,155,""PERSON_NAME""),(179,193,""JOB_ROLE"")]})"
"Senior Analyst - Wealth Management JP Morgan & Chase Co, Bangalore, India","(""Senior Analyst - Wealth Management JP Morgan & Chase Co, Bangalore, India"",{""entities"":[(151,165,""JOB_ROLE""),(208,228,""ORGANIZATION""),(256,265,""LOCATION""),(289,294,""LOCATION"")]})"
"Proficient in MS Excel, MS Word, MS PowerPoint and MS Access","(""Proficient in MS Excel, MS Word, MS PowerPoint and MS Access"",{""entities"":[(163,171,""TECH_SKILLS""),(198,205,""TECH_SKILLS""),(232,245,""TECH_SKILLS""),(275,284,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Oracle Hyperion Essbase and CORE,"(""Oracle Hyperion Essbaseand CORE"",{""entities"":[(149,173,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Oracle Fusion CRM and Oracle
Sales Intelligence","(""Oracle Fusion CRM and Oracle Sales Intelligence"",{""entities"":[(145,162,""TECH_SKILLS""),(191,216,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Lead Financial Analyst – FP&A
Oracle Corporation, Bangalore, India","(""Lead Financial Analyst - FP&A Oracle Corporation, Bangalore, India"",{""entities"":[(146,175,""JOB_ROLE""),(198,216,""ORGANIZATION""),(244,253,""LOCATION""),(277,282,""LOCATION"")]})"
"Received a sport award by Mr
Ganesh Ramaswamy, Sr Director of
Finance, EMEA","(""Received a sport award by Mr Ganesh Ramaswamy, Sr Director of Finance, EMEA"",{""entities"":[(171,190,""PERSON_NAME""),(217,228,""JOB_ROLE""),(254,261,""DOMAIN""),(283,287,""ORGANIZATION"")]})"
"MBA – Finance San Jose State University
","(""MBA - Finance San Jose State University"",{""entities"":[(130,133,""EDUCATION""),(159,166,""DOMAIN""),(187,212,""COLLEGE"")]})"
"Associate- Finance & Accounts Vedanta Ltd, Goa, India","(""Associate- Finance & Accounts"",{""entities"":[(157,175,""DOMAIN""),(195,206,""ORGANIZATION""),(234,237,""LOCATION""),(261,266,""LOCATION"")]})"
Bachelor of Commerce Northeastern University,"(""Bachelor of Commerce Northeastern University"",{""entities"":[(128,148,""EDUCATION""),(172,195,""COLLEGE"")]})"
Financial Advisor (Internship) Imperial Wealth services,"(""Financial Advisor (Internship) Imperial Wealth services"",{""entities"":[(172,189,""JOB_ROLE""),(213,223,""JOB_ROLE""),(247,271,""ORGANIZATION"")]})"
New sales metrics dashboard created in Oracle Data,"(""New sales metrics dashboard created in Oracle Data"",{""entities"":[(206,212,""ORGANIZATION""),(270,275,""DOMAIN""),(300,307,""DOMAIN"")]})"
"Azure experience will be plus (Azure Function, Azure Blob Storage, Azure Key Vault, CICD pipeline)","(""Azure experience will be plus (Azure Function, Azure Blob Storage, Azure Key Vault, CICD pipeline)"",{""entities"":[(215,220,""TECH_SKILLS""),(271,285,""TECH_SKILLS""),(312,330,""TECH_SKILLS""),(357,372,""TECH_SKILLS""),(398,412,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Strong SQL Server hands experience SP, Functions, Queries, UDF, Indexes etc.","(""Strong SQL Server hands experience SP, Functions, Queries, UDF, Indexes etc."",{""entities"":[(200,210,""TECH_SKILLS""),(253,255,""TECH_SKILLS""),(282,291,""TECH_SKILLS""),(318,325,""TECH_SKILLS""),(352,355,""TECH_SKILLS""),(382,389,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"5+ years of experience in Microsoft Dynamics 365 customization development, .NET, and Azure Services.","(""5+ years of experience in Microsoft Dynamics 365 customization development, .NET, and Azure Services."",{""entities"":[(244,266,""TECH_SKILLS""),(319,323,""TECH_SKILLS""),(354,368,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Development experience with C#, WEB API, ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, LINQ, MS SQL, JavaScript, jQuery, PWA, HTML 5, CSS 3 and Bootstrap.","(""Development experience with C#, WEB API, ASP.NET MVC, Entity Framework, LINQ, MS SQL, JavaScript, jQuery, PWA, HTML 5, CSS 3 and Bootstrap, React JS."",{""entities"":[(284,286,""TECH_SKILLS""),(313,320,""TECH_SKILLS""),(347,358,""TECH_SKILLS""),(385,401,""TECH_SKILLS""),(428,432,""TECH_SKILLS""),(459,465,""TECH_SKILLS""),(492,502,""TECH_SKILLS""),(529,535,""TECH_SKILLS""),(562,565,""TECH_SKILLS""),(592,598,""TECH_SKILLS""),(625,630,""TECH_SKILLS""),(660,669,""TECH_SKILLS""),(696,704,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Development experience in Microsoft Azure Services Service Bus (Queue/Topic), Function, Web Jobs, Redis Cache, Key Vault, Blob, Application Insights etc.","(""Development experience in Microsoft Azure Services Service Bus (Queue/Topic), Function, Web Jobs, Redis Cache, Key Vault, Blob, Application Insights etc."",{""entities"":[(297,321,""TECH_SKILLS""),(347,372,""TECH_SKILLS""),(399,407,""TECH_SKILLS""),(434,442,""TECH_SKILLS""),(469,480,""TECH_SKILLS""),(507,516,""TECH_SKILLS""),(543,547,""TECH_SKILLS""),(574,594,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Writing automated unit test cases (preferably using Nunit & Fake xrm frameworks),"(""Writing automated unit test cases (preferably using Nunit & Fake xrm frameworks)"",{""entities"":[(215,231,""TECH_SKILLS""),(274,279,""TECH_SKILLS""),(307,326,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Samantha Ruth - SR DATA ANALYST,"(""Samantha Ruth - SR DATA ANALYST"",{""entities"":[(148,161,""PERSON_NAME""),(189,204,""JOB_ROLE"")]}),"
"Worked extensively in Development Reports and maintenance projects of Power BI. I know SAS, R, Qlik Sense, Power BI and Basis SQL.","(""Worked extensively in Development Reports and maintenance projects of Power BI. I know SAS, R, Qlik Sense, Power BI and Basis SQL."",{""entities"":[(193,201,""TECH_SKILLS""),(240,241,""TECH_SKILLS""),(268,278,""TECH_SKILLS""),(305,313,""TECH_SKILLS""),(349,352,""TECH_SKILLS"")]}),"
"San Jose, California linkedin.com/in/samantha","(""San Jose, California linkedin.com/in/samantha"",{""entities"":[(137,145,""LOCATION""),(169,179,""LOCATION""),(202,210,""ORGANIZATION"")]})"
"Base SAS, R, Power BI, Microsoft Excel, SQL, Python,  JavaScript","(""Base SAS, R, Power BI, Microsoft Excel, SQL, Python,  JavaScript"",{""entities"":[(135,136,""TECH_SKILLS""),(150,158,""TECH_SKILLS""),(188,196,""TECH_SKILLS""),(223,238,""TECH_SKILLS""),(265,268,""TECH_SKILLS""),(295,301,""TECH_SKILLS""),(329,339,""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
"Sr Data Analyst- Deloitte - New York, USA","(""Sr Data Analyst- Deloitte - New York, USA"",{""entities"":[(132,148,""JOB_ROLE""),(171,179,""ORGANIZATION""),(208,216,""LOCATION""),(240,243,""LOCATION"")]})"
"Sr Process Executive - Microsoft Corporation, Washington, USA","(""Sr Process Executive - Microsoft Corporation, Washington, USA"",{""entities"":[(137,157,""JOB_ROLE""),(182,203,""ORGANIZATION""),(231,241,""LOCATION""),(265,268,""LOCATION"")]})"
Python is the latest technology,"(""Python is the latest technology"", {'entities': [(0, 6, ""TECH_SKILLS"")]})"
Python has a very wide scope.,"(""Python has a very wide scope."", {'entities': [(0, 6, ""TECH_SKILLS"")]}),"
"Ram is expert in python""","(""Ram is expert in python"", {'entities': [(0, 2, ""PERSON_NAME""), (17, 23, ""TECH_SKILLS"")]}),"
Python is the base language for data science,"(""Python is the base language for data science"", {'entities': [(0, 6, ""TECH_SKILLS"")]}),"
